<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>software on AWS Serverless on .NET</title>
    <link>https://sergiutalnaci.github.io/tags/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in software on AWS Serverless on .NET</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 20:00:50 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sergiutalnaci.github.io/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Present live camera feed in PowerPoint slides over Teams or Zoom</title>
      <link>https://sergiutalnaci.github.io/posts/live-camera-feed-in-powerpoint-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 20:00:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergiutalnaci.github.io/posts/live-camera-feed-in-powerpoint-slides/</guid>
      <description>STREAM Camera in PowerPoint Necessary software to install  OBS Obs websocket server PowerPoint OBS scene switcher  OBS Install OBS from here: Obs download link
OBS websocket server For websocket server, you can find the file by scrolling all the way down, Install OBS websocket server plugin from here: Obs websocket server github releases.
Download the installer that matches your OS, or unzip the contents of the ZIP file into the folder where you installed OBS (C:\OBSINSTALLPATH\obsstudio).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://sergiutalnaci.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 20:00:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergiutalnaci.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Whom is this blog for? AWS with dotnet using C# This blog is the about the life of a full stack software engineer experienced with dotnet and Angular, currently working with dotnet on AWS infrastructure at one of the largest toy companies in the world.
   Who am I? Software Engineer I studied software engineering since 2010 and have been working in the field since 2012 (student job). My first software engineering job on the SAP tech stack writing ABAP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
